{
  "French writingbeginner": {
   "Greetings": [
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'Bonne journée'", "options": ["Goodbye", "Have a good day", "Welcome", "Good evening"], "answer": "Have a good day" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'À bientôt'", "options": ["Good night", "See you soon", "And you?", "Until next time"], "answer": "See you soon" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'À tout à l’heure'", "options": ["See you in a bit (if meeting later the same day)", "Hi/Bye (casual)", "I’m doing well, thank you.", "Delighted to meet you"], "answer": "See you in a bit" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'Au revoir'", "options": ["Hello/Good day", " See you tomorrow", "Goodbye", "How are you?"], "answer": "Goodbye" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'Ça va bien, merci'", "options": ["Have a good day", " See you tomorrow", "I’m doing well, thank you", "How are you?"], "answer": "I’m doing well, thank you" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'À demain'", "options": ["Until next time", "Have a good evening", "See you tomorrow", "Not bad"], "answer": "See you tomorrow" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'Bienvenue'", "options": ["I’m doing well, thank you", "Welcome (as in, welcome to this place)", "See you in a bit (if meeting later the same day)", "See you soon"], "answer": "Welcome (as in, welcome to this place)" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'À la prochaine'", "options": ["Delighted to meet you", "Until next time", "Not bad", "See you soon"], "answer": "Until next time" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'Enchanté(e)'", "options": ["Hello/Good day", "See you tomorrow", "Delighted to meet you", "No worries"], "answer": "Delighted to meet you" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'Pas mal'", "options": ["I don’t know", " See you tomorrow", "Not bad", "No problem"], "answer": "Not bad" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'Comment allez-vous?'", "options": ["How much?/How many?", "Can you help me?", "How are you? (formal/plural)", "What is it?"], "answer": "How are you? (formal/plural)" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'À plus tard'", "options": ["I’m doing well, thank you", "See you later", "Delighted to meet you", "Good evening"], "answer": "See you later" },
     { "question" : "Translate to English: 'Bonne soirée'", "options": ["Have a good evening", "Until next time", "Hello/Good day", "See you soon"], "answer": "Have a good evening" }
   ],
   "Expressions": [
     { "question": "S’il vous plaît", "options": ["Thank you", "Please (formal)", "You’re welcome (casual)", "Excuse me (to get attention)"], "answer": "Please (formal)" },
     { "question": "De rien (duh ree-ahn)", "options": ["Don’t mention it/It’s nothing", "You’re welcome (casual)", "Gladly/Willingly", "Bless you! (informal)"], "answer": "You’re welcome (casual)" },
     { "question": "Avec plaisir", "options": ["Thank you", "Please (formal)", "With pleasure", "Cheers!"], "answer": "With pleasure" },
     { "question": "Bon appétit!", "options": ["Enjoy your meal!", "Please (formal)", "You’re welcome (casual)", "Excuse me (to get attention)"], "answer": "Enjoy your meal!" },
     { "question": "À vos souhaits!", "options": ["Don’t mention it/It’s nothing", "You’re welcome (casual)", "Gladly/Willingly", "Bless you! (after a sneeze, formal)"], "answer": "Bless you! (after a sneeze, formal)" },
     { "question": "Merci beaucoup", "options": ["Thank you", "Please (formal)", "Thank you very much", "Cheers!"], "answer": "Thank you very much" },
     { "question": "Santé!", "options": ["Don’t mention it/It’s nothing", "You’re welcome (casual)", "Gladly/Willingly", "Cheers! (to your health)"], "answer": "Cheers! (to your health)" },
     { "question": "Je suis désolé(e)", "options": ["It’s not a big deal/No problem", "I am sorry (for a mistake/bad news)", "Bless you! (informal)", "Excuse me (to get attention)"], "answer": "I am sorry (for a mistake/bad news)" },
     { "question": "Ce n’est pas grave", "options": ["Pardon me/Sorry (for bumping into someone)", "It’s not a big deal/No problem", "Gladly/Willingly", "Bless you! (informal)"], "answer": "It’s not a big deal/No problem" },
     { "question": "Il n’y a pas de quoi", "options": ["I am sorry (for a mistake/bad news)", "Pardon me/Sorry (for bumping into someone)", "Don’t mention it/It’s nothing", "With pleasure"], "answer": "Don’t mention it/It’s nothing"  }
  ]
 }
}
